With all that's gone on since I came to the Kawai Complex,
<(宇佐)河合荘に住んで
色々あって 俺と先輩の距離は…>
the distance between me and Senpai...
河合先輩 まだ帰らないんですか？
Kawai-senpai, you aren't going home yet?
<微妙に あいたままです>
has actually increased.
(田神)宇佐 帰ろうぜ
Usa, let's go.
≪(田神)あの人 同じｱﾊﾟｰﾄだっけ？
狙ってんの？
You live in the same apartment as her, right?
Trying to score with her?
バカ！ 聞こえるだろ
≪(田神)お前 変わった趣味だよな
Idiot! She'll hear you!
You have bizarre taste.
はッ？
≪(田神)いつも１人で本読んで➡
What?
She's always reading books by herself,
暗いし 愛想ないし
友達いないっぽいし
and she's moody and antisocial.
She doesn't seem to have friends, either.
<狙ってるとか 好きとか
そんなんじゃなくて>
I'm not trying to score with her,
and I wouldn't say that I'm in love with her.
<ただ もう少し
近くに行けたらって>
I'm just hoping
to get a little closer to her.
I'm home.
ただいま
≪(シロ)おかえり
Welcome back!
Episode Three
Why Do You
Usa-kun, something arrived for you.
≪(住子)宇佐君 あれ届いたわよ
裏庭にあるから
It's out in the backyard.
おおッ！
貯金崩して奮発したんすよ
I spent all of my savings to buy this.
いつか この愛車の後ろに
彼女を乗せて
My dream is to ride in the sunset
夕焼けを背に 優しい時間を…
with my girlfriend sitting on the back.
(麻弓)イヤッホ～
ごきげんだね…って コラ！
You're in a good mood...
Hey!
持ち主が
まだ またがってもないのに
It's my bike, and I haven't even sat on it yet!
何だよ ケチ
Why so stingy?
初モノ信仰は
心とシモの小ささの表れだぞ
People who always want to be first are said to be
lacking in tolerance, and lacking down there.
何の話だ
しかも初２人乗りまで奪って
What are you talking about?!
You even stole the first double ride!
What? You want to ride double?
えッ ２人乗りに憧れてんのか？
つか まだやったことないの？
私が学生んときは…
You mean you've never done it before?
When I was in school...
ああ うん あのころはホント…
Yeah, things were good back then...
Wait, was that the high point of my life?
えッ あれピーク？
Is this for tying stuff down on the rack?
これは 荷台用のロープか
Was that really the high point of my life?
(シロ)へ～ 丈夫な縄だね➡
This rope is sturdy.
よし！
て 何してくれてんの あんた！
Done!
What do you think you're doing?!
あ～ クソッ 取れねえ
Damn! I can't get it off!
(住子)シロ君 縛るの上手だから
Shiro-kun is good at tying things up.
廃品回収で
新聞出すとき助かるのよ
He's very helpful when we need to throw out old newspapers.
How do you make old newspapers that indecent?!
何すか そのハレンチ古新聞
よってたかって
俺のささやかな夢を…
Everyone's trying to crush my simple little dream...
We're back.
(彩花)ただいま 何の騒ぎ？
What's all the fuss about?
おッ おかえりなさい
Welcome back.
(律)ただいま
I'm home.
I-I think I like the sound of "I'm home" coming from her...
<なッ 何かいいな これ
｢ただいま｣だって>
You bought a bicycle?
自転車買ったの？
律ちゃん徒歩通でしょ
Rit-chan, you walk to school, right?
これから乗せてってもらったら？
Why don't you get him to take you on his bike?
I'm okay with that!
俺は構わないっすよ 荷台もあるし
There's even a rack on the back!
It's just about time for dinner.
≪(住子)そろそろお夕食ね
律ちゃん手伝って
Give me a hand, Rit-chan.
I forgot...
It feels like I'm getting closer, but I'm not.
<仲良くなれそうで なれねえな
こんなんばっか>
Stuff like this always happens...
律ちゃんが好きなの？
えッ！
Do you like Rit-chan?
It's not like that!
そうじゃなくて
ただ 普通に仲良くなれたらって
I just want to get to know her better!
Since, you know, we live in the same place and we go to the same school!
ほら 同じ住人で高校も一緒だし
話したらおもしろそうだし…
I think she'd probably be fun to talk to!
<わッ ヤバッ>
Oh, crap!
I'm a little worried since she's always alone.
先輩 いつも１人で
ちょっと心配っていうか…
If they find out, they'll abuse the hell out of me!
<知られたら 絶対いじり倒される>
最後の いる？
すッ 住子さん手伝ってこよ
Was that last comment necessary?
I-I'll go help Sumiko-san!
そ～れ
Here I go!
What is this? For some reason, I feel like breaking something.
何かしら打ち砕きたい気分
宇佐君 前途多難だね
It's not looking good for Usa-kun...
いってきま～す
All right, I'm off.
今日から自転車通学っす
Starting today, I'll go to school by bike.
よかったね 強そうな自転車だね
That's nice.
Your bike looks very powerful.
What kind of comment is that?
何すか その感想
何となく…
It just seemed right.
先輩はずっと歩きなんですか？
うん
Do you always walk to school?
H-Hey!
ちょっと遠くないです？
Isn't it a little far to walk?
We're holding a normal conversation!
あの…
Uh...
Be casual. Very casual.
<軽～く 軽～く>
W-Would you
よッ よかったら
後ろ乗ってきます？
like to ride on the back?
えッ？ 絶対ヤダ
Absolutely not.
She shot me down cold!
でッ ですよね 俺なんかの後ろ
O-Of course...
You wouldn't want to ride with me.
すいません 変なこと言って
じゃあ お先に
Sorry I asked such a weird question.
I'll get going, then.
<違う そうじゃないの>
No...
It's not what you think.
It's not that I don't want to ride with you.
<恥ずかしくて
だって だって私>
It's just too embarrassing.
Because... Because I
本当はあなたのことが…
am actually...
Is that right?
なんちゃって～
おいおいおい
とんだ乙女だな 律ちゃん
You're such an innocent maiden, Rit-chan!
自転車くらい
乗ってやりゃいいのに
Riding a bike together isn't a big deal.
｢俺に乗ってく？｣だったら
ヤベ～けどな
It'd be bad if he asked you to ride him, though!
麻弓さん サイテー
いいね 青春
You're awful, Mayumi-san!
Isn't youth great?
I want to find the courage to invite a girl and be mercilessly shot down!
俺もあんなふうに勇気出して
誘って 容赦なく断られたい
シロ君ならサドル引っこ抜かれて
投げられそうね
If you tried inviting a girl, she would tear off the seat and throw it at you.
≪(シロ)ご褒美 痛み入ります
≪(彩花)でも 宇佐君かわいそう
The best reward!
This is all too complex for Usa-kun.
Because he lives in the Kawai Complex!
河合荘だけに！
≪(彩花)彩花がﾀﾞｼﾞｬﾚったみたい…
Hey! Don't make it sound like I was trying to be punny!
知ってます？
Did you know?
この河合荘ってもともと
私の祖父の持ち家なんです
The Kawai Complex originally belonged to my grandfather.
そうね 私は借りて
大家をやってるだけで
That's right.
I'm just managing the place.
正式なオーナーは
律ちゃんのお母さんね
The official owner is Rit-chan's mother.
I'll exercise my privilege as the owner's relative
to increase your rent by 50%.
それもいいかもね ウフフ
That sounds like a wonderful idea.
彩花がちゃかすから
≪(彩花)麻弓さんだって！
It's your fault for teasing her, Sayaka!
You joined in, Mayumi-san!
Would you like to ride on the back?
《後ろ 乗ってきます？》
≪(シロ)律ちゃんごめんなさい！
Sorry, Rit-chan!
<そう仲良くないのに
２人乗りはねえわ>
Why would she ride with someone she barely knows?
<先輩 変に思っただろうな>
That probably creeped her out.
<こういう気まずいときに
図書当番だし>
And naturally, at an awkward time like this, I'm on library duty.
Library
<いるかな いるよな…>
Is she there?
She probably is.
Well, even if she is, I doubt she'll notice me anyway.
<まあ いたところで
俺のことなんて>
宇佐君
Usa-kun.
今朝は ごめん…
Sorry about what I said this morning.
えッ…
だから その…
I mean, I feel bad about being
絶対嫌とか言っちゃって
悪かったなと思って
so harsh when I rejected you.
Though I still refuse to ride with you.
実際 絶対嫌なんだけど
そッ そうすか…
I-I see...
でも あの…
宇佐君が嫌ってわけじゃ えっと…
But, um, it's not that I have anything against you...
Just...
I like to read while walking.
私 歩きながら本読むのも好きで
それに 男子の自転車って何か…
And...
Riding on a bike with a boy sounds... well...
Especially if it's you...
宇佐君だと特に その…
河合荘の人達にからかわれたり
めんどくさそうで
I don't want to deal with the others in the complex teasing us.
そうなると
宇佐君が嫌なわけなんだけど…
And you wouldn't want that, either...
先輩 先輩 もういいから！
気持ちは受け取ったから
Senpai! Senpai! It's okay!
I understand how you feel!
S-So there you have it. Please carry on as normal.
そッ そういうことだから
今後はお構いなく
えっと お元気で
そちらさんも
Um, take care of yourself.
You, too.
We'll be seeing each other again at dinner...
<近づいたのか 何なのか>
I'm not sure if I've gotten any closer to her,
<それはもう どうでもいいや>
but it doesn't matter anymore.
She's so weird.
<変だ ホント ああ 確かに>
Yeah, I guess it's true.
Maybe I do have bizarre taste.
ちょっと痛い… やめろ 彩花
Hey! That hurts!
Cut it out, Sayaka!
You always leave yourself wide open.
≪(彩花)麻弓さん 無防備すぎ
Shiro-kun, are you all right?
≪(シロ)住子さん もっと
Harder, Sumiko-san!
何 このカオス居間
What is this, a room of chaos?
もう 足踏み疲れちゃった
跳んでいい？
I'm tired of stepping on you!
Can I jump instead?
この腹 いいでしょ 女同士だし
Look at all this flab!
Quit fondling me!
What's the problem? We're both girls.
大体 フラれたとか決めつけんなよ
麻弓さん 分かりやすいもん
And don't assume that I was dumped!
But you're so obvious about it.
You don't even care that you don't match.
ありえない組み合わせ 平気だし
何すんだ バカ！
≪(彩花)いいでしょ 女同士だし
Wh-What are you doing, stupid?!
What's the problem? We're both girls.
Oh, yes! Right there!
お前の女同士の許容範囲は
広すぎんだよ！
You make it sound like anything goes if you're both girls!
あッ 宇佐 ボケッと見てんなよ
Usa, stop staring at me.
私はそんな やっすい女じゃな…
I'm not the cheap and easy kind...
of... girl...
Look at me.
見ろよ
何で殴るんすか
Why did you punch me?!
宇佐君に当たるのやめようよ
Don't take out your frustration on Usa-kun.
やっすい女じゃないんだから
I mean, you're not the cheap and easy type, right?
What's wrong?
どうしたんですか？
あッ…
別に 何でもないから
Nothing.
Nothing's wrong.
Nothing's wrong?
She was crying...
That's my phone.
電話
Incoming
取らないんすか？
Aren't you gonna answer it?
元カレか
しかも あの反応
It's her ex...
And judging from her reaction...
未練あるんだろうな
She hasn't gotten over him.
An e-mail?
メール？
Sorry
I want to hear your voice
別れた女にすがって
みっともねえって思っただけ
I was just thinking that he's pathetic to come crawling back to an old flame.
断じて ニヤけてなんかいません
I wasn't smiling or anything.
And how can he sound so desperate
久しぶりだっていうのに何だよ
こんな
せっぱ詰まってるみたいな…
when it's been so long...
自分で言って
ときめいちゃったよ この人
She just made herself swoon.
Why do you make it so easy for guys?
どうして そう男に都合よく
気持ち くみ取っちゃうかな
だって…
Well...
Incoming
Man, he won't stop.
まったく うるせえな
But if I ignore him again, he'll keep calling over and over.
でも また無視すると
何回もかかってきそうでウゼ～し
あ～もう めんどくせえ
Man, what a pain!
Hello?
Mayumi-san had a big smile on her face.
今 麻弓さん
すっごい笑顔だったけど
やっぱりか
ダメ男と知ってて何で…
I knew it...
Why is she like that, when she knows he's a jerk?
分かんないですね
I don't get it...
今なら ちょっと分かるかも
I think I understand... now.
She understands?
<聞き間違いだよな？>
Did I hear that right?
What's with that weird look on your face?
おッ 何だよ 変な顔して
So, are you getting back together?
で より戻すの？
Of course not.
そんなわけねえだろ
しつけえから相手してるだけ
I'm just humoring him since he won't give up.
If he was three-timing you,
３股だったってことは
今 ２股してるの？
does that mean he's two-timing now?
He said he put an end to that after we broke up.
私と別れて すぐ切ったって
嘘くせえよな
Sounds like a lie to me.
It's not like it makes any difference.
だから どうってわけじゃねえよ
私は
そんな安い女じゃないんだから
I'm not the cheap and easy type.
ごちそうさま と…
I'm done eating.
もう ホントしつけえな やれやれ
Man, he won't give up.
She's so easy, I can't bear to look her in the eye.
麻弓さんがちょろすぎて
直視できない
すっかり ほだされてるね
She's gotten attached again.
自分で気づいて
諦めないといけないんだよね
She has to realize it and give up on her own...
部屋戻る
I'm going back to my room.
<う～ん どうもおかしい>
Something's wrong.
<まさか彼氏とか 好きな男とか>
Surely she hasn't gotten a boyfriend or fallen in love...
No, she's still always by herself.
<いやいや 相変わらず１人だし>
<気のせいだ 気のせい>
It must be my imagination.
シロさん 何作ってるんすか？
What are you making, Shiro-san?
へへッ 連射ゴム銃！
Rapid-fire rubber band gun!
おもしろそう
麻弓さんも喜びそうでしょ
That looks fun!
Mayumi-san loves stuff like this, right?
シャボン玉のときみたいに
破局前提で作ってるでしょ
Just like the bubbles!
You made that because you're expecting her to be dumped?
いや～ そんな
Nah, of course not.
ただいま
おお 宇佐
I'm home.
Oh, Usa.
ちょうどよかった 住子さんに
夕飯はいらないって言っといて
Good timing.
Can you tell Sumiko-san that I don't need dinner?
会うんですか？
Are you going to see
Three-Timer?
変な名前つけんな！
Don't make up weird names for him!
別に よりを戻すとかじゃなくて
I'm not looking to get back together.
会いたいって しつこいから
メシぐらい…
He keeps saying that he wants to see me,
so going to dinner can't hurt.
Mayumi-san.
麻弓さん シロさんが
連射ゴム銃作ってましたよ
Shiro-san made a rapid-fire rubber band gun.
えッ すげえな
That's impressive.
And we're having oyakodon for dinner.
あと 今日の夜は親子丼です
いいな…
That's nice.
いってらっしゃい
Have a lovely time.
<うん？ 何だあいつ>
What's his problem?
Welcome back, Rit-chan.
ああ 律ちゃん おかえり
出かけるの？ 股三と
Are you going out with Threeman?
誰だよ
Who's that?
Mayumi-san, are you happy?
麻弓さん 幸せ？
えッ
そんなこと聞くキャラだっけ？
Do you normally ask questions like that?
何となく 聞きたくなっただけ
I was... just curious.
They're all acting so weird.
You don't eat much, Mayumi.
(元彼)麻弓って少食だよね
そうかな？
You think so?
<違えよ イタメシ苦手なだけだよ>
Hell no. I just don't like Italian.
Didn't I tell you when we were going out?
<つきあってたとき
言ってなかったか？>
Are you feeling nervous?
≪(元彼)もしかして 緊張してる？
As if.
<するかよ！>
Juuuuust kidding.
≪(元彼)な～んてね
Don't drag out the "just"!
<｢な～｣のばすな！
いかん イラついてきた>
Damn, he's starting to piss me off.
Say, once you're done drinking that, let's go to my place.
≪(元彼)それ飲み終わったら
もう俺の部屋行こうよ
At least try to sweet talk your way there!
Um, not yet...
えッ もう少し…
≪(元彼)ああ
Ah, you must want dessert.
さてはデザート食べたいんだろ
はッ？
Girls really love sweets.
女の子って
ホント スイーツ好きだよね
It's cute and all, but let's order a cake for takeout.
そういうとこ かわいいけど
ケーキはテイクアウトしてさ
He's showing me no respect!
Sorry, did I get your hopes up?
ごめ～ん 期待させちゃった？
I would have been willing to spend the night if I was having fun,
楽しかったら朝までつきあっても
いいかなって思ってたけど
but frankly, I already want to go home.
正直 もう帰りたいし
それに 好きでもないのに
あの演技すんの しんどいし
Besides,
it's not worth the effort to put on that act for someone I don't even like.
やめとくね
So forget about it.
Bye-bye, then.
じゃあ バイバ～イ
<ああッ！ シロから
連射ゴム銃借りときゃよかった>
I should have borrowed Shiro's rapid fire rubber band gun!
Is there any oyakodon left?
親子丼余ってる？
食べたくなったから帰ってきた
I came back because I felt like having some!
あッ あれ…？
Huh?
今日はオムライスよ
We're having omelet rice today.
I just made it up.
適当に言いました すみません
I'm sorry.
Welcome back!
おかえり
りッ 律ちゃん
Rit-chan!
You're crying for my sake?
<私のために泣いて…>
律ちゃ～ん
Rit-chan!
Who is that?
Was Rit-chan always that type of person?
律ちゃん
あんなキャラだったっけ？
本？
Books?
The main character attracts jerks the way Mayumi-san does,
主人公が麻弓さん似の
ﾀﾞﾒ男ｷｬｯﾁｬｰで しかも大作
and it's a long series.
律ちゃんて
本に影響されやすいのよね
Rit-chan is easily influenced by books.
さっきまで麻弓さんに
すごく共感してたけど
Not long ago, I could really relate to you,
今は 大人なんだし
もっとしっかりしてって気持ち
but now,
I just feel that you need to be an adult and get your act together.
私の涙を返せ！
Give back my tears!
Senpai is definitely weird.
<先輩に好きなやつが
いるわけじゃなくて>
And I'm no better since I feel relieved that she doesn't like anyone right now.
(男)待てよ
好きって言ってくれたじゃん
Wait!
You said you liked me!
But that was... Please let me go!
だから それは…
離してください
何でだよ 急に
Why did you change your mind?
You're hurting me!
痛い！
さッ 彩花さん？
S-Sayaka-san?
うッ 宇佐君…
Usa-kun...
≪(男)何だ お前
彩花ちゃんとどういう関係だよ
Who are you?
What's your relationship with Sayaka-chan?
どッ どういうって…
Wh-What's my relationship with her?
単なる同じアパートの住人で
ねえ？
We just happen to live in the same apartment...
Right?
そッ そう…
Y-Yes...
Why are you looking away?
同じ…
We just... l-live in the same apartment...
<なぜ口ごもる…>
Why are you mumbling?
迷惑 かけないで
Please don't make any trouble for him.
No need to remind me.
<やめて その念押し>
いや マジでそれだけなんすよ
No, really! That's the truth!
<うわ～ どうしよう
我ながら嘘くせえ>
What the hell...
Even I think that sounded like a lie.
≪(男)こんなクソガキのどこが！
What's so special about this brat?!
彩花 お兄ちゃんほしかったから
I was drawn to you because
憧れてたっていうか…
I always wanted an older brother...
So...
その… 誤解させてごめんなさい
I'm sorry if I gave you the wrong impression.
But I've realized that love feels completely different.
でも 憧れと恋は まったく逆で
Why are you looking at me when you say that?
<なぜ こっちを見ながら言う？>
甘えてくる年下の男の子って
かわいくて
I think it's cute when younger boys try to be affectionate.
Before I knew it, I was...
気づいたら 私…
Wh-What's going on?
<なッ 何だこれ…>
テメエ 彩花ちゃんに
ここまで言わせてだんまりかよ
Hey, you have nothing to say after making Sayaka-chan say all that?
俺 置いてきぼりで
状況が悪化の一途を…
I'm totally lost and the situation's only getting worse.
Wait! Sayaka-san!
ちょ… 彩花さん
Sorry.
That's it?!
軽ッ
もうお前黙れ
You can shut up now.
一発殴って終わりにしてやるから
I'll let you go after I punch you once.
I haven't said anything yet...
始まってもないんすけど…
ゴチャゴチャうっせ～よ
Just shut up!
何だ？
What the hell was that?!
せッ 先輩
S-Senpai!
え～っと…
Um...
すいません
風でピュ～ンと飛んでっちゃって
Sorry, the wind blew my book into you.
えッ
そんなピンポイントな突風が？
Wait, the wind was that accurate?
はい ピュ～ンてビックリです
Yes, I couldn't believe it myself.
あと そこ入りたいんですけど
And I need to go inside.
Oh, right.
おい
ですよね…
Hey.
Of course.
テメエ まさかあの女子高生とも
えッ？
Are you also putting the moves on that girl?
さっきのは明らかに
かばってたろうが！
She was clearly helping you!
She was helping me?
<先輩が俺のことをかばって…>
ぶっ殺す！
I'll kill you!
宇佐君 どうしたの？
Usa-kun!
What happened?
あんたもな！
I could ask you the same thing!
災難だったわね 宇佐君
That was quite a disaster, Usa-kun.
いや～ 俺が学校近くに
捨ててあった古雑誌の紐を解かず
Yeah...
I was struggling to pull a dirty magazine out from a bundle
of old magazines near the school without breaking the ties,
エッチな本を抜こうと
四苦八苦してたら 職質受けて
when a policeman asked me,
｢また君か｣って
家まで連行されたのが
"You again?"
and brought me home, which ended up working out.
功を奏したな
昔の男子中学生みたいな
頭悪い行動に助けられて
It's humiliating to think that I was saved by the stupidity
of a guy who thinks like a middle school boy.
屈辱的です ありがとう
Thank you!
迷惑かけちゃって
ホントごめんね 宇佐君
Sorry I got you involved in that, Usa-kun.
彩花さんが悪いわけじゃ…
何言ってんだ バ～カ
It's not your fault.
What are you talking about, you fool?
この女のせいに決まってんだろ
It was clearly her fault.
こいつは好きでもねえのに
She likes to toy with men she has no interest in.
粉かけていじくるのが
趣味なんだよ
彩花 そんなつもりじゃ…
Sniffle... That wasn't my intention...
That "sniffle..." crap annoys the hell out of me!
とかウゼえっつってんだろ！
でも彩花ちゃん
外でのことは口出ししないけど
Sayaka-chan, I won't tell you how to behave outside,
but it's not good of you to bring trouble here.
ここにトラブルを持ち込むのは
感心しないわ
今度また
同じようなことがあったら
If you do something like this again, I really will increase your rent.
ホントに家賃上げますからね
ごめんなさい
今後ないよう気をつけます
I'm sorry.
I'll make sure it doesn't happen again.
<家は秘密にしていたのに
ツメが甘かったな>
I kept my address a secret.
I guess I wasn't careful enough.
<反省箇所 そこか…>
That's the lesson she's learned?
そもそも たぶらかすのやめりゃあ
いい話だろうが！
You should just stop seducing guys!
たぶらかしてなんかないもん
向こうから勝手に…
I'm not seducing them.
They come to me.
蜜置いて網張っといて 何ぬかす
Don't lie! You're using your honey to trap them!
断っても諦めてくれないし
They keep coming after I reject them.
麻弓さん
断るいい方法 知りません？
Mayumi-san, do you know a good way to make them go away?
うわ～ ムカつく
心底ムカつく！
I'm mad! She's making me so mad!
じゃあ 目の前で
ﾒｲｸ落とせばいいんじゃないかな
Why don't you try removing your makeup while they're watching?
シロ
Shiro...
Thank you for going hard on me...
ハードなの ありがと…
先輩
さっきはありがとうございました
Senpai!
Thank you for helping me earlier.
さっき？
殴られそうになったとき
Helping you?
You threw your book when that guy was about to punch me.
本投げてくれたでしょ
ああ 門の前で邪魔だったし
Oh, he was blocking the entrance.
でも助かったから
But you saved me.
ありがとうございます
本大好きなのに投げてくれて
Thank you very much.
You threw one of the books you love so much...
But weren't you scared?
しかし 怖くなかったです？
俺 ガクブル
I was shaking like a leaf.
べッ 別に…
N-Not really.
You really amaze me.
先輩すげえな… そういや
Oh, yeah, you also tried to save Mayumi-san before.
前に麻弓さん
助けようとしたことあったっけ
You can be pretty reckless.
先輩 結構ムチャしいですね
気をつけてくださいよ
You should be more careful.
But you saved me, so...
でも助かったし いや～
ホントありがとうございました
Really, thanks so much!
あのままだったら俺
確実に殴られて…
If you hadn't stopped him, I would have been socked—
That's enough.
もう いいから 大げさ
You're overdoing it.
先輩 顔赤い
Senpai, your face is red.
うッ 宇佐君がしつこいから
大したことじゃないのに
That's because you won't stop!
It wasn't a big deal!
えッ だって実際助かったし…
But you did save me...
だから もういいって言ってんの！
I said that's enough!
Wait, Senpa—
ちょっと先輩…
<何で？ 怒らせた？>
Why?
Did I make her mad?
Wait, don't tell me...
<あれ？ まさか…>
<お礼言われて照れちゃったの？
何それ 何なの>
She's embarrassed because I thanked her?
Really? What's with that?
Why are there flowers around him?
何あの花 うわ～ すげえ殴りてえ
God, I wanna hit him so hard.
宇佐君 彩花ね 心配してたんだ
Usa-kun, I've always been really worried.
律ちゃん １人で平気そうだけど
本当はすご～く寂しいと思うの
Rit-chan acts like she doesn't mind being alone,
but I think she's really lonely.
So please be there for her.
だから 力になってあげて
I know you can do it.
宇佐君なら絶対いけるよ
あんなに打ち解けてるんだし➡
She's opened up to you so much,
彩花 応援してる
and you have my support.
彩花 お前…
Sayaka...
Seriously...
ホント性格悪いな
You're evil incarnate.
What? Why do you say that?
え～ 何で？
≪(住子)彩花ちゃん
Sayaka-chan.
As I mentioned before,
(住子)さっきも言ったけど
トラブル持ち込んだり
If you bring trouble to the Kawai Complex, or make any mischief here,
河合荘の中で遊んだりしたら
I might get just a little bit angry.
私はちょ～っと 怒っちゃうわよ➡
A
We'll
all
stay
pitiful
tomorrow
shi
ta
mo
bo
ku
ra
wa
mi
n
na
ka
wa
i
so
u
A
Preview
I was wondering why Senpai has been giving me and Shiro-san funny looks...
先輩が俺とシロさんを見る目が
おかしいと思ったら…
What's wrong, Usa?
どうした 宇佐
誰ですか 先輩に男色小説薦めたの
Who gave Senpai homosexual books to read?!
Homosexual? You mean men on men?
ボーイズラブか
Well, since Rit-chan gets so deeply involved in her books,
(彩花)律ちゃん本に夢中になると
入り込むから➡
I wanted to see what would happen if she read some romance.
恋愛小説ならどうなるのかなって
恋愛なら
何でもいいってわけじゃ…
That doesn't mean any kind of romance would work...
しかも カップリングの相手が
シロさんて！
And she's pairing me with Shiro-san!
律ちゃんのためだ
一肌脱いでやれよ
C'mon, this is for Rit-chan's sake. Break out of your shell!
(シロ)仕方がないな…
この縄で俺を好きに縛っていいよ
I guess we have no choice.
Usa-kun, use this rope to tie me up however you like!
Episode Four
For the Time Being
それはジャンルが違うから却下
Nope. I'm not interested in that genre.